Next step is to create the file and just click here
and click plus symbol here.
Type the same name, mission,
D-E-H-H-O-F test.
I say script Python. It's a Python file, right? Do py.
I'll enter and I'll paste
where at copied in the previous step right here.
And then very important, you see the one here.
It shows it is not saved.
So make sure you actually save it, save this.
Next I'll use AI to enhance the script.
So I put the prompt here and I'll just run this.
Let's see what happens. Okay,
so we have, uh, the code ready.
We'll check the code. Take a glance at it.
It still reads 2024. Yeah, we gotta change this, right?
We gotta be changing this to read two years data.
So we'll ask it to update.
Can you update the code to make sure
it reads 24?
It's full data in the curated folder
and not just 24 and one.
It's all good. Now, I'll provide this code to you.
You can use it and run the uh, next step, which is
to create the glue video job.
So use the code from the video that you're seeing now.
The code is above, below the video,
so let's create the glue etal job in the next step.